phuocub.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy • PhuocUB

## Affiliate links policy

 **Disclosure** : Please note that we are run  some of the affiliate links and I will earn a commission if you purchase through those links (at no extra cost to you). I recommend that you do your own independent research before purchasing any templates, themes, product or service.  We just provide information or guideline related to what you are searching or finding on our website, we recommendation you to read more about specification templates, themes or products before you make a purchasing.

## Ads privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Collection of Personal Information

When visiting PhuocUB.Com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of PhuocUB.Com then you may contact us at  
phuocubdotcom@gmail.com
